Welcome to the night, the car is laid out for show
Star shine is so bright, watch the secret sun fall
There's magic in her hands
Whisper what the future holds
Dance to the mystery
With a rhythm
Yeah, yeah, yeah
Flow
Hearts in the balance, every card an open door
you're a member? Well, I appreciate you being a member. I'll say that one second. But because you
like said that, I made it longer. I mean, it's like, I don't like being told what to do. Thank you.
They're a compilation CD. You know, I have stuff for free right now on my mix cloud.
If you want to like go listen to this stuff. You like me? Okay. Hold on. I need to figure out how
I just like, and I have trouble trusting people sometimes.
But hey, you like me, that's all I need to know.
Okay, I mean, I came kind of to this show.
Okay, guys, I want to thank Skribbles and his wife.
Okay, so Skribbles, I went over to this show.
You know, I like Skribbles.
You know who Skribbles is, guys?
He's uh, he's a really cool streamer. He's he has like a tattoo on his face. What's it say?
It's like fuck or something. It's really cool. It's cool. And
Yeah, he um, I
Went over there. I was like one of the first people in the chat and he's like, hey, he's like oh my he's like
Oh, I remember you. He's like, oh sake. He's like, oh you changed your name. He's like, do you think you could do reading for me?
And I was like sure and
So I did it. I thought hopefully I did a good reading for him and then I did for his wife
I also I saw a saint today same was really cool. I
just want to say
Wow, it's really cool to you know
Have people that are nice to you have people that are cool to me
So anyway, I really want to thank them and I'm gonna try to post their channels on
I'm gonna actually make sure I post their channels in on my side. I'm working on stuff
On the uh, the second verse or whatever. Oh, I think it's it if they want it there
Or actually, I'm I think I'm just gonna like try to put all the people that I really like on there
but
Hopefully they don't like it. I think it's uh, yeah, we'll just tell when they're all in the stuff
Anyway, let's see. How's everyone in chat doing? Let me see the Howard's room playing million interest. I don't know
It's like what do you do?
He's a lot of stuff. Oh, there's Tony. Hey psycho. Hey, by the way, Tony, thank you so much for the
The two bags of fertilizer. That's perfect. It's just perfect for my garden. That's just a perfect amount
You didn't not too much not too little
You know, I had two nice free bags of fertilizer outside my door
I'm unfortunate the guy that came by for the lawnmower. I guess I think
Somebody else must have gotten the lawnmower or something like that
So
Unfortunately, I don't actually I don't even have a lawn or lawnmower. So the guy was very disappointed
anyway, I
Do have another inch or though. No, I'm just kidding
What is it? Oh my gosh, what happened to my screen?
The fuck hold on
Something's not right something is this right? Oh, there are you okay. Is it right?
Okay, that's better. That's better. Okay, um, what was that what happened? Oh
Kind of blurring into the back of it a whole long second. There we go
Okay, that's better
Well, I need to put a background. Okay, let's figure it out here
Capricorn when you see it at all
How is your day, I'm sorry I like left a little bit earlier today because it was
There we go
Yeah, I I kind of got distracted by like
Trying to figure some stuff out. So hi Chanel. I couldn't help myself. Where's everybody? Why is everyone so quiet? Oh
No, not more hate watchers
Chanel's here, I thought Tony was here earlier. Who's this Tony persons? Hi psycho. It's raccoon gang. Ah, you're fine. You're fine. I
Okay, lowrider Chanel
Look he's nice
Okay
Meow meow meow meow, okay, let me turn that off
Yeah, so in case you didn't hear I was I went to scribbles today on his backup channel
He's yeah, he put me on stream yard. It was really cool. It was he's really super cool. I let him hit in his Mrs. Scribbles
They're really cool, and I wish them the best and thank you for letting me read for you guys and
Being so cool to me and then a saint. Thank you for
Also, like saying hi to me. Good to see you guys. It's been a little bit crazy lately. I don't know. Wow
It's been really crazy lately, but
Hopefully everyone's getting along tonight
don't think Tony sent me the fertilizer though I mean not the Tony in the room
but Tony did it's like Beetlejuice you just don't say the name or then it they
appear I fix that there you go I don't know what's kind of weird about oh I know
cuz I freaking changed the size of everything hold on a second
That's why I was like way way off. Okay. I need to change it. Okay. There we go like that
And then uh-oh, okay keep changes and that's fine
I can close that. Okay
Sorry
Hi, what's up money for 20 there is perfect. Okay. Now I figured it out. Okay. I can go like
Okay
I'm going to put Scribble's chat or his show in the chat so you guys can check him out.
He's real.
One time I called him and I was like, hi, Scribble's, I'm the guy you dated in jail.
He never went to jail.
And I never did.
But he laughed.
It was funny.
He's really, he is a good looking dude though.
He has a wife. I don't know what how I find him like this YouTube
Check out this guy's channel, but you know, he's really cool. It means like you mean I'm not very cool
He's cool. I think so check out
Like if they don't think he's like someone like me like the you just troll. Oh, he was on too
Yeah, well, here's a backup channel. Here you go guys
You will be
Probably maced if you mess with them because he actually one of the first things I saw was when you went to Vegas and some
He was like looking at this like these like it's showgirls kind of like
looking at their butts and stuff and then
Their pimp or something came running up and he's maced the pimp in the face. It was better than it was almost good
Oh, also, I was accused channel yesterday and he was nice to me too. So it was like, you know, oh
Also
When I went to Saints, he was like say psyche. He's like you've been on trip kick
He's like I saw you in a couple things. He's like I saw you like and I was like, yeah, I've been clipped like 10 times
So hey, hello, Jamie
There's a there's I think this might be a backup channel, but you can of course find another channel through there
I'm gonna put saint 10 to saints channel. Oh
Hold on there. This is Saint
Um, Saints also very cool, dude.
Shit.
I can't.
I guess it was a, but I guess it was a mod over at Saints.
Guess.
Our old nemesis all over Jabroni.
That's a, I, I, I, I hit him.
I mean, I, no, I mean, I, I just hit him from me.
Ah!
You like those, oh, they're so cool, Jamie.
Yeah, Jamie, since I'm really close up.
That's Saints channel.
Who else we see I'll show you I'll show you Q's channel too. It's fish taco
10 I think something like that. I don't know if he did he name that after me
What an honor. Can you believe people are like naming? Oh shit?
people are like naming their their like
Channels after like the inside joke about that's so cool. I'm like wow
But today I was like listening to KK's and I was like, oh my god, Christine's there beat is there Tommy didn't I'm like
I'm like, I know all these people and unfortunately all them hate me, but it's kind of funny because it's like
It's a small world, right? It's like I was like, I just know it
I know like practically like a lot of people and everyone knows me but I so I didn't say anything. Let me see fish taco
10 that it
I don't know. Let me check. It's my phone bringing you. Maybe it's the number 10. Let me see.
Oh yeah, here it is. He's actually on. Oh, I'm not going to say anything. Don't go over there right
now. I mean, I'm streaming here, but you can check him out later here or check him out whenever you
Fish taco 10, maybe it's not after me or something. I don't know. Oh
Oh, I
Think did I make fish tacos famous on?
What is fucking with my?
Computer I'm so sorry guys. Just one second. That's why I have to like play a million song. Oh, it's that's why it's over because
There we go. That's better. Okay. Now we're now we're now we're getting somewhere now. We're getting somewhere
There we go. Perfect. Perfect. Perfect.
There we go. My Capricorn.
Okay.
Yeah, I'm gonna look. Oh, yeah, I want to, I have to go, I have to save them and I'm gonna put them in a video, Jamie.
So, I got some channels up. Let's see. There's only 11 people. Oh, everyone left when I posted the channel. Shit.
You want to come up?
They don't and I do have a new like video to premiere. I haven't heard them really hurt here. It was innocent. Oh
That's not it is it?
Why isn't there sound look
I think I have a worse feeling about it.
Do you guys hear me okay?
It is the never ending story. Let me see if the sound's broken or something.
Is that what I do?
Isn't there sound?
Fuck.
Something's wrong.
Okay, well, I fucked everything up, okay.
Everyone's leaving. I mean it's like I'm a mess right now. I'm gonna eat my Big Mac and shit. Fuck
Feel like I'm like all alone
How's this for background
I feel like something's not quite right.
Do you ever get a weird feeling?
Do you ever get the feeling you're being watched?
Just kidding.
Oh, here we go.
Someone's coming to comment.
Oh, Jamie.
Let me see if the other sounds work.
Oh, hey, hello.
What's up?
I can see a hello, hello.
So let me see if I can show you any of my work.
That's not, I mean, that was like a while ago,
but I'm sorry, a little bit.
There's no place to stay.
Whether it's her house, whoever pays the bill,
she gave you a place to stay.
Not broken.
You're an ungrateful son of a bitch.
No, look, look, like right now,
look, look, look, look, look, look, look, look, look, look.
That turned off the,
I look, fit me in bed, right?
You hear me?
Do you hear me?
Is anyone hearing me?
What is this?
I live in a project.
Does anyone hear me?
Do you hear me?
Say one in the chat if you can hear me something's wrong. Oh
The volume was off
The volume was off. It was on mute. Okay, it should work now. Now we can try
Now we can play the video. Okay, here we go. This is a new video
Just as rides on whispered gales
In the ninth the law of stars is ripped
A pilgrim's flame that won't submit
Pluto carves the bones of fate
Saturn forges Jupiter inflates
Balancing worlds in each hand
Streels of the night sky
Chains of sun
galaxies
skills of the night
A balance keeper, draped in gold
Philosopher, destroyer, king
A pilgrim forging everything
The sacred law you guard
Divine
Your heart's the temple's soul
The shrine
Let's fight
I mean, it was just kind of slow.
I mean, I did my best.
OK, I was just experimenting.
OK, just trying to get something out.
Yeah, everyone, scroll up a little bit
and subscribe to Q, Scribbles, and sync.
You liked it?
OK, cool.
It's a cool little.
I was experimenting with the cap cut video but it's like really hard to edit in it because it's
really really tiny and so I had the screen like all blown up and it's like so I needed to
I need to get better at it but okay thank you sir very much enough okay um so what happened
So I told you I went to cake while I was just in K case for like just watching
I don't know what's going on. There's this woman in chicken cakes or something like that. I
Mean if she was like and Tommy I was like, oh my god
I know all the people Christine was there beat it was in there. I was like, oh my god
I just know every I know a lot of people I got I told you I got some fertilizer
Someone got free fertilizer delivered to my doorstep how convenient, right?
And some guy came looking for a lawn mower,
but I don't have a lawn mower or a lawn.
I don't know why he would think that I would have a lawn,
like, well, I'm sure,
and I know somebody told him I had a lawn mower,
but like, does it make sense
that I would have a lawn mower like in my, I don't know.
Just very strange.
He was really nice.
He was like a nice little Asian guy
and he's like, oh my God, I'm sorry.
And I was like, tell the cops.
Also, I told you, somebody came by this morning,
like, hello at the door.
And I was like, yeah?
He's like, I'm here for the scrap metal.
I was like, oh, there's no scrap metal here.
And he's like, what?
Yeah, I just talked to you on the phone.
And I was like, that wasn't me.
Call the guy back.
He's like some kind of weird con artist
that's like sending people on wild goose chases.
The guy's like, motherfucker, he was so mad.
Because I guess he's like he's telling people that there's like valuable scrap. I mean how valuable can scrap metal be like is it?
Valuable like how much is it? Does anybody know how much it like and like what like what do they think I would have like I?
Don't know like where they see there's no no scrap
There's that I don't take like a young lumber yard or something like that. It's like a nice like little manicure
House, I don't know why I'd have scrap metal like this is my house or something. It's just kind of stupid
But uh, you know people believe anything these days
So anything else anybody hear anything interesting, but it was pretty cool when I went to say and she was like, oh, I saw you on trip kick
Yeah, he's like are these like are people being mean to you copper house value? Yeah, but that's like in a in India
There's like copper wires or copper like a hey, what's up? What's up x Tracy in a India
There are people would people die because they
They like turn off the I guess it's like railroads or electricity goes through all these copper wires
And then it's like when they turn it off people try to steal it
But then it might turn back on if they do the timing wrong
He needs to back. Oh, yeah, I know isn't it ridiculous J dog. It's ridiculous, but it's like the people are nice
I actually meet some nice people, but they're like always disappointed. They're like, oh my gosh
There's people just coming thinking that there's gonna be some kind of like great
Dang, but I did get free fertilizer. So I guess and I have a Big Mac tonight. I got my McDonald's guys
I think I'm like living on McDonald's. Oh
That's my neighbor. I'm like living on McDonald's now
That's good for you. I remember I used to eat McDonald's and I get sick
Am I like, I'm not gonna get sick.
I've been eating it every day, probably.
And I eat the fries on the way home
and I just like, I get a large fries for like a dollar
because you can use the app
and you can get the fries for $1.25.
Always use an app for like restaurants
because you can save so much money.
Like it would cost like probably $5 to $10 more.
Don't eat fast food.
It's it's kind of a treat make a cock-shaped scrap metal outside your door and say there it is
Oh, hold on I mean, I hear some making a lot of noise outside. I need to look at my window
Hold on
It was just my neighbor, just my neighbor.
I was thinking though, you know that lady,
like her name is like, her name is like,
I think her name is Shrek, oh no, no, her name is Shannon.
Yeah, yeah, she,
She was like, oh, I don't watch Psyche.
She's like, okay, she has seen me do readings.
She knows about my like TikTok advertisements
that is like really buried in all my millions of shorts.
And, you know, and then she like,
she said, and he does, he gets his e-bike.
So she knows about the e-bike.
And then she knows about, well,
then see what she doesn't know is that, you know,
I do spoil the kitty cats, right?
But,
I mean, it's like, how does she know?
Oh, you like Big Macs?
Me too.
Here's your little mouse.
I like these because then the cats don't bring in mice
and eat them and stuff here.
Here you go, babe.
Here.
Put the mouse on.
Play with it.
Look at his pink little ears.
Isn't he cute?
He's so cute.
Yeah, Big Macs are good.
Look at.
I mean, I get the fries, big Macs, I get, usually,
what I get is like, I get a coffee.
I've had like five coffees today.
Hey, what are you doing?
What are you doing?
Come and say hi here.
Here.
Uh-oh.
Get the bouncy, get the bouncy, get the bouncy,
get the bouncy.
It loves little toys.
Get the little toysy.
Here.
Hi, what's wrong?
Oh!
yeah he's a cute little cat. Nothing fragile about this Yankee. Look at this beautiful, huh?
I mean it looks like he should be in a museum. Look how like beautiful waxy. I like the sauce on
this. I did get this like um I got the McRiddle this morning and I got this like weird sauce on it.
It kind of smelled weird but it tasted good. It's like a spicy like weird sauce on it. I don't know
It is kind of expensive because I think it was like 20 bucks practically for like the two coffee like a like a Frappuccino
Large coffee large fries and a Big Mac
Was almost like $18 or something stop eating at McDonald's, but it's so good
It's really good. Oh
The fries are gross after
Hmm Donald is good
It's like a familiar taste, you know, I
Don't know what we're gonna do now. I just I this one's gonna
Do a panel I guess here come on up you want to come say hi
Let's have a show let's do a show. Hey, how about like I do a free panel
Maybe I'm not so desperate for fish tacos today and dick that I'll do a free panel, right?
All right, hey, thank you.
I mean, these people are just terrible.
Well, like, if I do a sponsored panel,
is there something wrong with like sponsorships?
I mean, it's not like I'm putting commercials,
well, there are commercials in the show,
but that's YouTube doing that.
Not like I'm making a ton of money from that.
I think I'm making a little bit of revenue from the ad, so.
McDonald's is good and you don't have a refined palette. You are accustomed to trashed
Yeah, I'm accustomed to trash because you're here all the time Jacob Chavez, but you know what? I think I'm getting a better taste
Gonna kick you out
And if you don't know about McDonald's coffee McDonald's coffee is bomb, but I don't like you I
Don't like you the only thing I like about you is you kind of look like a joker
That's why I kind of kind of confuse you for him, but you're not him
And so that's disappointing
So I'm gonna kick you out of the room go away
Hey, look, I want to show you something too
Very weak. Yep. Yeah, like your face
But look look what scribbles called my show
Tarot reading with psyche awakens you like the reading I think you like the reading oh
What are you saying?
I'm still talking about it.
It's really cute, huh?
He's really cool.
Yeah. Yeah. Bye-bye.
Let me see how the, let me just look at what the chat was talking about me. Let me see. It says...
Reflection of the bowl leaked on the rude's dog new ground bicep. I don't think they're talking about me
That I came oh
Someone in 420 says has me blocked again
Ground elk hits different in the chili. I
Don't know that they're talking about I think it was like but it is it is you can check out my reading there
Oh, they're talking about pussy farts?
I don't know what you're talking about.
But it's called Tarot card reading with Psyche Awakens TV.
You can just check out, I'm gonna maybe share this.
I'll share his, aw, I just got a message.
I wanna share this chat though.
If you wanna check out the reading,
I did it at the beginning of his show for him and his wife,
or his, yeah, his wife and,
It was really, really, really good.
I mean, it was just like, he was really cool
and it was, I think I did a pretty good reading.
Check out this live.
That's his.
If you wanna go to watch that instead, it's fine.
I just want people to enjoy the night.
You just have to, it was at the very beginning of the show.
That was my appearance, right?
It looks a little bit quiet in here.
So if anyone wants to come up to the stage, you're welcome.
I don't like really have that much
Kind of like I might be taking a little break
After today not not that I was like, I mean it might just be gone for a little bit like maybe like
I'll try to come back tomorrow. I don't know. I just I think it may be better if I
If I take a little break
Because it's like it is kind of like emotionally
exhausting and stuff like that lately and I have been like
I've streamed every day except for like three days this year.
Hi, you calling me Psycho?
You know that Psycho's one of my favorite movies?
Oh, and that stupid woman, Shannon or Sharon or whatever.
I was like, oh, the Queen of Wands.
I was like, this is a Norman Bates' mother card.
If not calling a Norman Bates' mother card,
literally the card had Norman Bates' mother corpse on it.
I guess she doesn't know, like, you know,
Hitchcock movies or whatever, but that's one of my favorites.
I need a break.
Too much YouTube is not good, right?
Oh my gosh, it's exhausting, it's exhausting.
I try really hard though, right?
I've been trying like, I've been, no,
we're not trying too hard, but I've been like, you know,
putting a lot of effort into my show and stuff.
To like and people say oh, it's just easy even Alex was like. Oh my god. Alex was like, I'm a nice guy. Thank you, Tony
You're a nice guy, too. Thank you for being friendly
Even I bet Alex McQueen was like, oh my god. He's like, how do you do it?
He's like I was confused without even anybody on the panel and I mean Alex can even figure out how to turn on the camera
I don't think because
Or else you just don't really want to you still want to see the bed of the bad Tony. Oh, yeah
well he's around all the time he's like his name is allied master computer he's in
kates he's in betas um he's in kks he's he's like on all the other stuff right thank you
yeah i mean i used to stream a lot more i used to stream like for 12 hours and i get drunk and
I would actually wake up and start streaming and then I would like stream until I passed out
Like that's how much I used to stream
It was but that's it's not good because I need time to like, you know
You know for myself and stuff, but it was it was fun
But yeah, so but in those days you probably did get some like embarrassing footage of like, you know
I was just on the camera all the time, but
So maybe I picked my nose once. I don't know
So sue me do I know Billy Hayden
Sounds familiar is Billy Hayden a
Streamer or oh, he's a good guy who comes here son. Oh, yeah, I recognize that name. I
recognize the name
Yeah, I have mostly good people like today
I had like you know Natalie and gaudi were on the panel
But there is like the chat was like it was just the same troll over and over and over and over and over
It was this guy Mike call Mike Hall
And he was coming on all these different names
Just being annoying and every time I saw him speak I would just hide him and it's like that's so many accounts, right?
a lot of accounts
But anyway, I think it's like, okay, so yesterday was 9.30, right? It was September 30th. So 9.3
0.0. That's like
93 million. How about acid? I don't remember. I don't know acid. So the we're like 93 million miles away from the Sun
So that's 9.3 also in Thelima. There's like he's subbed to you and then flipped out
Okay, I came out there's someone named acid trip or something like that. Oh my gosh guys
I have the coolest I found the coolest like I'm in you know an Instagram
I came across like some really cool stuff like the trippy stuff and so look at this stuff
I've been saving on my on my computer on my
Tablet you see dog on pictures
You see if I can get in my photos it's like trippy as hell. Oh, yeah, I do have them look like watch this one
Yes
I have to get it on my screen.
Look at that shit.
It looks even better.
I'll try to get it on the screen.
Let me see if I can get it up.
I'll see if I can save it and ring it on the screen.
That'd be so cool.
I could do that.
Because there's really, I need some hallucinogenic mushrooms or something
because it looks so cool.
I think I need to go to my other account.
Let me see.
Google Photos.
Let me see if this works.
Oh bodybuilder. Oh, yeah, yeah, let me see
Right, okay, here it is. Let's see if I can save this one
Okay, yeah, it's 14 seconds. Okay, let me see download on the desktop. Okay, where is it? Let me see
Users John down. Okay, let's see if I can put it up watch this shit
I don't know if it saved the whole thing.
Video, say users,
John.
Desktop.
Downloads?
Where'd it go?
So I'm sorry, I'm like way,
I got here to watch this.
Or
Was that it it's pretty cool
Yeah, you need more mushrooms.
I'm sorry if I gave anybody epilepsy.
I think I gave everyone like a new kind of epilepsy
after that.
Yeah, we need some mushrooms.
Did you look at that?
Yeah, I have a bunch of them.
I don't know why there's only one safe.
Let me see if I have any more.
I remember my glasses on.
Oh, I do.
Hold on.
Let me see.
Oh my God.
Okay, I do have more here. Look at this one. This isn't longer
This one you say oops, that's a rim reaper nice. I'm gonna try one more. This one's this one's a little longer
Has Rick and Morty in it. I think
Okay, are you ready guys guys if it's like if things like
If hallucinating disturbs you, you might want to look away from the screen right about now.
Are you okay? Is everyone okay? Please don't sue me. Don't sue me. Are you okay?
Oopsie. You're okay? Okay. Yeah. Yeah, you might want to get some acid or something.
Guys, I have a lot more, but I'm not going to play anymore right now because,
whoo, I think that got me high just looking at that. I want to watch that one more time.
Thank you for watching.
Good, I'm sorry about that guys. Oh my god. Everyone laughs in like five people left. Oh my god
I mean guys, it was cool. I look at like now. There's 11 people. Well, that's fine. Either they either they died or they left
I don't know. Hey Barbara. What's up?
You just peed your pants you just peed on your pants. Oh my gosh
Yeah, that's pretty cool. I'm a little bit dizzy, but
Okay, it was just a short thing. I mean guy. I told you to look away
You're supposed to look away, but how did it look so many people left? It must have just like slammed off the computer. Oh
Gosh, I need to take off my jacket. Do you like my shirt? Oh, this is very cool shirt. It says. Oh my gosh
Oh, it says
It says
Not enough sage for this shit there I have enough
Everyone's having a seizure everyone's
But it's like there's such cool stuff on Instagram. I don't know how I came across that you like that stuff. Hey Barbara
Let's see is everyone that should be mod. It looks like everybody in the room is a mod. Okay. That's good. You're not okay, Jamie
Oh, no, Jamie. I heard from a old friend of mine. Actually, I'm not gonna say who it was, but yeah, we have a it was kind of I
Was told
Guess it's not gonna really like work out. Maybe I don't know. I mean it might I was like a Jamie made some cool stuff, too
You don't know what tomorrow will bring so don't stay mad for too long
Learn to forgive and love with all your heart. Don't worry about people that don't like you enjoy the ones that love you
Oh, that's like a pretty oh, I know I recognize that person kind of and I was thinking Jamie
I know I remember when we all were friends like, you know, not Jamie knows what I'm talking about. We were all like
Got along at one point and it's like I don't know what happened
Is Janet here? What's up, Janet?
Janet you want to come up tonight? I want to yeah. Oh, yeah, you want to come up? I want to talk to you
I mean not that we need to think bad
Oh, oh good. It's all good. I just need to talk to a friend and like a lot of people are too shy to come up, you know
They love like, you know, I'm not like, you know
Making me ready. Oh, I know sponsor panel or anything. I just want to talk to people
Hold on
Anybody's welcome too, but if you want, you know, of course, and also, like, you know, people, some people maybe want to do one-on-ones, like, if it gets, like, because, you know, like, I don't, I don't like the feeling of having all these people yell at me on the panel, and so some, like, if people, as someone bothers people, if someone's, like, bothering people, like, you know, if Alex starts yelling at people and stuff.
Then I won't mind like kicking him off and just doing one-on-one and then like maybe having him on like a little bit later
One-on-one, but I think I don't know. I haven't seen him in a couple days. Where'd he go?
I don't think he's hidden in the chat
But he has his own show now. I think he was trying to do his own lives and stuff again. Oh
Here we go. Hi
Janet
Sorry, I was on mute. Hi. How the hell? I'm doing okay. How are you?
I'm good. Thanks for asking. Thanks for inviting me up. What's going on?
Yeah, I mean, it's like, you know
Like for all that's been said, it's like, you know, you
You know, I've had you know, we've I've had ups and downs with people
But it's like I never had
Such a bad time as I have with some people like we know and it's like it's just like so crazy like how
I was, I don't know, it's, I'm just like happy
that I have such good people like remaining.
It's like, after all the fireworks explosions
and everything, like who's staying,
always look at who's remaining,
like who's still there like with you and stuff like that
and who's causing the problem and stuff like that.
Right.
It's like, and so thank you for staying by me
and like, you know, for giving me for like,
you know, my mistakes and like,
My stupidity because I've made mistakes, but it's like some people are willing to
We all have just people don't take accountability for their mistakes
Yeah, I mean it's like and it's like
You saying that because I told you I'd stay by your side
I told you not even though we went through what we went through friends make it to the end
Yeah, and you never like and from all I've been thinking, you know, oh this person said this
About me and you know that
That was what they were doing. I didn't need to do that if I needed to say some you I can come sell you
I can turn on my camera like you do and we can have that
But I don't want to talk bad to you, I don't want to talk nasty because nothing happened when them people tried to attack us. I stood up.
You and her said, no, let's just do what they want and look what happened.
So I didn't judge anybody for what they did, but I didn't go talking about folks. Folks did that to me.
See, they keep trying to play victim perpetrator, but I don't go for nobody. I don't have to. I stand in my own.
I am Empress. I'm her.
Right, so I've never changed from the time I met you. I'm still her
Yeah, it's just like it was like looking back. I was like pretty much like just like I
Was in like some kind of state of trauma and it's like and it's like I mean not from you
We all go through the echo. I call it. It's just that when we come out
Right, and we're either different or you're gonna be like them. They're in it. They're chaotic demons
They're like basically dead souls. They're it's clung to the alcohol. You know when you were drinking
But you know, the most high wants us to go through some things sometimes so you can understand where people are at in their life.
When I came out here six years ago, I used to drink every day, I used to cuss folks, I used to do it.
But I changed, and I learned that again, if you really are a content creator, you're building content, you're helping people, and you stand on that.
You come out here, you give life and energy to people, they respect you, they love you, they shouldn't be telling you what to do.
You know, but you'll learn learn the ones that love you learn the ones that hate you and
Again, they're all just kind of like in the matrix, right?
So even in the matrix when they were all on that ship, they were all in brown outfits
Keanu wasn't any different than the driver the black guy or or the lady
But when they suited up and they got into the seats and they locked in and they came into this world
They became what they wanted and they saw the people that were the ones
So there are ones that are deliberately trying to make you fall when you were
No one let's say and you were just running around in chats networking for yourself. You knew what you were doing then
So even if you thought you were no one, then you were because you made that name to start growing.
No one made you. People helped you and then tried to use it against you.
So let's be honest. They didn't make you. I didn't meet you from her or anyone else.
I met you at a sector where you were up there with a Halloween mask on coming up 20,000 times on that panel,
never giving up, determined to make sure you were going to make them people laugh.
And he found me, I asked, and followed you.
Because I was like kind of like put out there that it's like,
I was like, I was like, nobody.
And then until I met this one other person,
and then it's like, and then, and then I
was like, manipulation and narcissistic people are real.
And you're very vulnerable to that,
because one thing you told the enemy was, I need friends.
You didn't say I want true individuals who will, you know, keep me in line.
You said I wanted friends and so people said, oh, well, let's pick that friend card and be a buddy troll to him.
Let's, let's show him that friends are, you know, doing what they did.
But you said today that your friendship meant that you see it now.
You see what really means a lot to you and who really cared.
You shouldn't let no one change your mind.
No one should be telling you who to be friends with or how to move psych or none of that. They should be
Respecting what you do the people that care about Janet. They don't tell me what to do
They tell me how they feel if something's done
They're hating the fact that they lying on my dog, but you remember when my dog was sick
I sent you pictures of my dog and I said I can't come to your show psychic remember that night
I said I can only come an hour because my dog was sick
The back legs wasn't working the baby was shutting down because she was getting old with cancer, right?
But they mocked that I knew that wasn't like whatever it was wasn't true
And that's like and then it's like when they I like examined, you know, I didn't I didn't need to examine because I remember like
just like every all the dates were all it was just like it was just like right and I don't have no
criminal record they can't pull that to that record for real that ain't no real and you're not
you're not like I mean that's that would be like the most monstrous thing but if people are so willing
to believe like even like that's obviously they want that to be the truth so that it doesn't hurt
for what they really are yeah see if you lie on someone it makes them feel better about the lie
They just rather lie money is showing a video. He said can you play the video?
What is it? It's I put the link in the chat if I can play I can't copy from that
I can probably maybe I don't know. What is it money though? I didn't even know what it is before I
Before I play anything, but yeah, um, so that's an example of what they'll do to you. They'll cause stories
You know
Shannon in law yeah, I do I do you see the clip of the reading and stuff
No.
OK, it's really short, but she's like...
I worked seven days a week, like last week, so...
I mean, I played it before, but this woman,
because it's so kind of, it's a trip kick,
this woman, like,
said some stuff about some stuff about,
kind of like, and she almost like,
even though she said horrible things about me,
she did kind of tell,
like, something interesting,
and I just want to get your opinion about
one of the things she says about me,
like how I came into the thing.
I don't think, whatever she says about, you know, Alexandra, it's complete bullshit, but what she says about somebody else and why, you know, what, you know, what this, okay, I don't know, you have to see it, it's real quick, it's a really short video, this is interesting, oh my gosh.
Okay
You know you that bitch if you cause all that conversation so the celebrities have a certain way and you know this again
You're no you making videos on them. You're clipping and cutting your own content. It's different
People making videos on you. You're the star of the show regardless of its depicting. They're bad
Look at this guys. I didn't see this look at this
That's why same was like oh his saint today. I talked to me like oh my god
He's like I saw you clipped in like trip kick out videos, but look at this Jen. I didn't see this yet
Look at this look at this look at this
Me me this one has me in it
Okay, these top three right there. So this is what I want to show right here. So here we go
Yeah, I'll just this is interesting. You can see how I'm how it's kind of treated when I went to Kate's panel one day watch
What's what's going on?
Hey Kaseaki, why don't you come up and show us your fucking beta pose with your little American flag-thonged bitch?
Seas is cooking tonight!
The fucking weirdo?
Why don't you go lay in a fucking puddle a fucking god damn kitty litter fucktard?
You haven't realized you fucking bitch the only reason why she's over there
It's because you have an audience sometimes and she wants to fuck beta over you didn't realize her contents beta it ain't you face boy
It's not you and your little fucking weird-ass pussy cat you got over there.
I have a question for you, psyche.
Are you that broke that you actually have to charge people to open a fucking panel?
I mean are you really that goddamn broke that you have to charge people to start fucking
No, he's just that he's just apathetically disparate. Did you guys see his new advertisements?
Come join my popular panel. I'll give you readings, but I don't even know what the fucking death card means
But I can show you my fucking tank dressed in american flag in my baby
And that that is it. That is the real site. That is the real site people
And then we do, so you do what I say, you do what I say.
No, I watch.
We watch the fucking clip.
I watch fucking beep.
I watch fucking.
Jenny, I watch fucking trip kick because I'm watching four hours
of some gay guy pretending to be a psychic fucking beg
for money for fucking fish.
Get the fuck out of here.
I forgot what I'm on.
So fucking weird perverts all up in there all the time.
Fucking weird
Let me tell you something if Jimbo was up there telling women that the only way they could get up on the fucking panels
If they show their tits, they would fucking roast him
About being a sexual predator
Fucking psyche can sit up there and say well you can
If you show your fucking shlong you you're gross out motherfucker
He's laying on a fucking puddle of kitty litter,
fucking talking about how he's the devil.
You're a fucking weirdo, bitch.
The only reason why you get any attention that you do
is because you're an LOL now.
So, Shannon, can he come up here
and give you a tarot reading?
I'll pay for it.
Oh, please, allow him to.
I would love to fucking rip his little American flag
shit up his ass.
You hear that sight?
I say you five dollars for a tarot for Shannon.
You gotta come up here and do it.
Yeah, let's see how well you rigged here. Tell me what the death card's about again
Because you totally fucked that up
I don't know
You so you say he's been reading them wrong the whole time. Yes. He doesn't know what the fuck
How's he trying to act like he's a celebrity and people want to see him when he's looking
Tarot in his name he
with a bunch of old women, fucking cats, sleeping on fucking kitty litter, and writing a fucking e-buck
to get fish tacos. Are you guys really buying that shit?
Shut it. Shut it. You're killing him.
Give her a read if she say you don't read the cards right.
Oh my god.
Prove to us that you read the cards right inside.
Yeah, right.
Hey, that's fucking good.
Because I got Sarita's from you, man.
You giving me Rollerita's?
I'm going to tell you what they really fucking mean,
because he goes all over the place like he's fully shit.
He doesn't know what the fuck any of them fucking mean.
You know how long I've been watching Tarot?
Tell me again how the death card is.
What was it?
You said it was?
It was about something, someone in your life leaving you.
Are you talking about Santa Santa you can't tell me because I'm telling you I got I pay for readings from him
So you telling me that he read to me the wrong shit
The one fucking time I saw me and he said the death card was about leaving something behind or whatever
That's not what the death card is about. It's about new beginnings
It means the end of a fucking right cycle in your life in a beginning one
So I can tell you right now
Then he pulls out his little Disney princess cards,
talking some shit about the four of cups.
Motherfucker doesn't know shit about cards.
At least get out the key they give you
and it fucked hard and read what they mean.
Well, they need $5 for the cats,
yet I've never seen him buy shit for his cats ever.
I've seen him buy an e-bike.
I've seen him fucking ride to the fucking beach
and buy fish tacos.
I've seen him try to get the butcher's fucking phone number.
I've seen him fucking pull his legs up like he was a fucking female in his little fucking red, white, and blue panties.
But I'm seen doing shit by shit by lick fucking goddamn snatches of women that he think are more popular than him.
Hey, where's your trilogy out there? Where's, where's Psyche's beauties? Not one of those fuckers talk to you anymore, dumb shit.
And that's for a fucking goddamn friendship.
Here's the truth, Psyche. I'm gonna give you a fucking truth. You know what? You were you were cannon fodder
Be to brought you to be to brought those fucking people to your fucking place because she didn't want you to fucking have a real stream
She didn't bring you to saying man's
She didn't fucking bring them to fucking Cates. She didn't bring them
She brought them to your channel and none of us knew that
Fuck you were you were just one of her weirdos that she fucking had in her back pocket
So instead of losing her channel, she could fuck with yours. Good job
Such entertainment
Who is this first of all Shannon
What is this?
First of all, I pulled the cunt card for her, so she got that.
That's her first card, okay?
Yeah, exactly.
That's her only card, too.
I do know how to read
your car is a read-off so we can see what you can read
the right side yeah yeah let's see the card yeah let's see it work I can't
but it's not appropriate for Kate so I had more respect for Kate than to get
her up or shows the card I want to see between your legs and that's that
smelly snatched between your legs that's all of it well you wouldn't know what
Okay.
Wow.
You got me there.
You got me there, bitch.
Oh my God.
My cat's better than you, bitch.
Why don't you stay out here and play with me?
Why don't you stay out of pussy, and I won't smell like shit?
I don't even know you. Like, what are you talking about?
If you don't even know me, how can you talk?
You're talking about some character you see on...
This is Shen, and she's the queen of the... of Gen X.
She ain't queen of shit.
She's being able to see it. She's queen of shit.
I'm certainly not the queen you are, bitch, boy. That's for sure.
You'll never be the queen I am, bitch.
No, don't worry. I don't want to be you. I didn't realize that turning your couch into a fucking litter box made you
In my video
I don't know how she knows me.
How does she know so much about me?
She sounds, she's like, I don't know zero about her.
Well, because you get to lift because you're an LOL cow.
Sorry, Gembo, hold on.
Really? Well, milk me, bitch. Milk me.
How about some fresh grass? How about some green grass?
It really hurt. I'm really sorry.
I don't know if I can stay up here.
I don't know if I can stay up there, kid.
Okay. Go. Go be sad.
Go be sad.
I'm not a fucking employee member here.
You have to respect me a little bit.
Sorry, kid.
I had a premonition. I was going to hear some dumb
plot screaming about me on a show and then I came over here.
And I think I'm perfectly.
I'm perfectly.
I think all plots.
Yeah. Oh gosh.
Either way, make sure you pull out the key for the card.
So you actually know what they mean.
I don't need to wait for the garbage.
I've been doing tears and I was eight years old.
Okay. So by the way.
Yeah. And every year old is so gifted doing peril.
It started, it's called like, you know, you learn over the years.
Well, I've been doing tarot since I was two, so I win.
You haven't been doing tarot at all, have you?
Yes, I have.
I do tarot every fucking day.
Okay, well, you know you should be careful about the sparrow gene fellow readers the karma is really bad on that
Oh, yeah, okay. I'll worry about my karma as you're spreading your disease to the americans
Okay, give a show like how do you know you have the public fucking stream that everybody clips because you're a total retard
I have a reading party if you don't give me a fucking shut up. I'll give you a good reading
But if you don't want to shut up, then it's fine. No, no
Little mad
Do the reading, Syke, do the reading.
Yeah, it made me so, okay, so I will,
I'll do the reading.
Okay, this for Shannon, this Shannon's reading.
And so you received justice for something
in the recent past.
I don't know if that was a successful court case
or something in the recent past,
but you, something was made fair for you.
And you've also got like,
oh, you see all these options available to you now
because of this, but it's a lot of confusion
because of it, because there's so many,
you're going to want to pick the one
that you most gravitate towards.
That looks like something to do with love because there's like a two of cups and this is like, you know, two equals
Meeting and you know starting something that can grow into something bigger
You're also coming up as queen of wands. And so you've got a lot of good fiery power. This is also like the norman baits
mom card, okay, whatever
Also, because you are
Some more about that card
What's the more about the card? Well, it says courage, confidence, independence. It says norman baits is mom
That's what it's like, that's what it's like, that's what it's like, that's what it's like, that's what it's like, that's what it's like, that's what it's like, that's what it's like, that's what it's like, that's what it's like, that's what it's like, that's what it's like, that's what it's like, that's what it's like, that's what it's like, that's what it's like, that's what it's like, that's what it's like, that's what it's like, that's what it's like, that's what it's like, that's what it's like, that's what it's like, that's what it's like, that's what it's like, that's what it's like, that's what it's like, that's what it's like, that's what it's like, that's what it's like, that's what it's like, that's what it's like
there. Yeah. So that's, that's not a date. Okay. Lies some more because it's not going for you. Go
ahead. Okay. Well, whatever, whatever, I'm going to do this quick reading for you. Okay. Finally,
we have the 10 of, the 10 of wands, which means you've been carrying some burdens, you've been
carrying other people's burdens, maybe because you're in the screen energy, like a lot of people
go to you for help and things like that. No, you don't say. But it is very heavy. It's like,
how do you got burdens going on in the future? Shannon is correct. The queen of wands is passion,
fierce independence symbolizing someone who boldly pursue
their dreams with courage and enthusiasm this card encourages you
authentic self-embrace creative endeavors
Okay
Yeah, you're doing it since you were eight, but you can't even get the cards right.
I got all the cards.
You don't even know to look to see if the cards reversed, you fucking tarred.
I can pull them reverse or they're not reversed, you fucking tarred, okay.
Anyway, they'd come out reversed, they wouldn't just turn them upside down on my own.
Okay, well anyway, you know nothing about tarot, so whatever.
So okay.
You know nothing about tarot.
Okay, thank you, K, for having me on.
I guess that just leaves one score to seven.
You can't hit me.
Then let this be our final battle.
Okay.
Janet, what do you think?
Yeah, yes, dear.
I think that the editing was amazing.
That's positive.
I definitely feel like they showed the part
where they jumped on you about maybe not knowing the tarot.
And then, you know, in the end kind of put a little comedy spin on it, so it's a lot better than the ugly videos that are being made about me.
You know, I got to be a green woman that looks like the, like the garbage pale exorcist kid, but no, I think your videos are cool.
But the question comes in.
Why you feel like you have to, you know, defend yourself about tarot, you do it and it's good for you.
What's the problem? Ain't every tarot person different? I mean, they're questioning your card, your ethnic of it or something.
What? Everything you were fighting for because I don't feel like you can fight if you can't be heard.
What's the sense of screaming over people? You know you're true, so why bother?
I will go there, but I don't want to lose my voice over it. I want term by term. So you didn't get a turn
So what were you trying to say up there when you were talking like?
I didn't like I just went in the chat and then I she was I heard my name brought up whatever and I was like
You know kind of just like talking from the chat and then it turned into like oh come up and I'm
I do want to like I mean it's like now I feel bad because I heard this woman has like
You know she has one leg or something like that and it's a bit and I did see her show
She has literally like two people in her chat
The one of one of them is her mod and like literally just like all this
Things to be caddy and petty. Let's talk
Excuse me pirates actually had one ice too, so let's not
I didn't know she was like that I would ask the question was she right or wrong
Well, she's wrong. You know, I mean even what she said is like
Mean we have exactly what I said the car was I couldn't really talk you're not supposed to really talk over someone doing the reading
Right like and she had this other guy screaming. Oh, and I it was exactly what I said the cards were
Down to the Norman Bates his mother stuff. I just think it's like interesting
She's like oh well Bita just brought you or she just brought people over to your chat because she didn't want her chat
Like you know her show fucked us, but she wanted to fuck with your show
And I'm just thinking back to all the guests and so like it was just like all of a sudden
She knew word bad versus show she did
She never denied bringing over people she can't control the bad people she brought over I don't care for the girl
But let's be honest
She didn't bring them over here for them to mess up your shit. She knew they were
Not sure about that like I'm not quite sure about that
My opinion and because I was there at the time when she was doing it with you correct and again
She would open up your panel to help you
She was helping you her goal was to bring
Everybody that was over here from hers to you because you were doing the same type of shows
She did when she came to my show. She knew not them people weren't loud there
She she tried to bring them one time and we have oddly talked about no because I got people with
Ancides and things and they don't need to be triggered by that that stuff
Some of us, some of them can't handle that, right?
So she knew that it's not to care about your health.
You're being kinder, you're being kinder than I was.
I'm just being honest at that time.
I believe that she was really just
bringing people to help you.
But in return, there could have been something there.
I'm not saying you're not right.
I'm saying it's...
First, what I saw was her trying to bring the crowd for you,
to make it look like, oh my God, I'm bringing you numbers.
I'm this person that helped you, right?
So, because in return, then it'd be like,
well, I did this for you.
Look what I did for you, you know?
So that's what I kind of saw.
Maybe I'm wrong though.
I mean, you tell me.
Well, you know, I had a falling out with her
just yesterday.
I mean, I will never like Maracuda, bitch.
She's a lion too.
Too bad he wear it ass for her, but I mean this is what it is. She's a week. Oh
And you know
You know about this also
Yeah, you know, I
Don't know, but you know, it's good. Well, you know, maybe I should look at it more kindly because
I don't know. I'm just picking up a lot of pieces. There's a lot of people I have to I had to like cut out cut out of
Off of the show and it didn't take my show
I never asked you to come over to my show and bring your crowd
I never asked you why you didn't come to my show when I always came to yours
They never argued about none of that did we?
So again, people's intentions, that's what you should really be paying attention to, what were people's intentions when they're doing the things they're doing for you?
I don't know because...
Well, they tell you, manipulative people tell you.
When you didn't have this, I did that, there it is right there.
Looking back on some of the old episodes, because I do go look at them for clipping and stuff like that,
and now while I have thousands of hours of material, even though I deleted half of my streams,
I still have thousands of hours of material to go through, so many things.
I'm repressing or like, you know, especially when I would leave the panel or just disappear
I was like, you know, I was drinking a lot too, right?
I was just drinking a lot and it was I was having fun but watching back. It was like I was green
I was like and I was trying to be so nice and I didn't I have changed where I'm not like as
Nice as I was but looking back. I was like
Just like the new per I just didn't know anything about anything, you know
It's like I just didn't know what I was getting into and it's like oh I feel bad for like that guy
You didn't say you wanted football friends.
You didn't say you want to cheerleading friends.
You didn't say you want to Gothic friends.
You just said, you are a friend, friend.
I'll take any.
And here come the ones that came out of the darkness,
the little vampires, little demons and shit.
They said, oh, you need a friend.
Let's suck on this motherfucker and run him dry.
See if we can get him to do what they've made you almost do.
But you've survived, sweetheart.
I've just watched your progress plan.
You gotta stop talking to that crowd.
Remember, we're the show, we're the host.
And when we go home and close it,
you need to close the doors all the way.
They shouldn't have access to John.
John and psych are two different people when you start understanding that and stay ten toes on both sides
You'll be at peace of mind my friend and again you continue with your beautiful AI's and all your beautiful stuff around her
And you keep on asking for money on the YouTube channel that is monetized, you know, I mean like we're talking about
So that's what I do is like, you know, not only try different things and be successful
I've had some great months. I've had some shitty months
But it's like I'm still every month. I've been monetized
I mean, I've been able to catch you know catch up because I've made over like, you know
They're dollar threshold or whatever. I don't care what others say, you know the truth
You know what they did and again, you know what they continue to do. They'll smile in your face
So again, if you can't tell the truth.
Hold time, they're gonna take your place.
All right, so I got to run.
I got to get back to the real world, darling.
I love you too, darling.
Kisses.
Thanks for coming on.
I'll turn on my camera.
I know, turn on my camera.
Ah, wait, let's go the other way.
Hold on.
You stay strong too, and you know what?
You already got a friend in me, and you know.
It still didn't turn.
Thank you so much for just being my friend. Okay. I love you. There we go
Capricorn
The New Year's come in new things are coming just stand for something so you don't fall for everything. Okay, thanks for having
See that's people, you know, there are great relationships that I've made
I mean like see even like remember I thought like SIG was the biggest problem and like SIG is like turns out
he was like he's just kind of like a
Not really even
Not really even not that bad, you know, but there have been worse. Hey everybody
Do you want to have a seizure?
Thank you for watching.
Hey, I hope no one did, I was just kidding.
I didn't really want anybody to have a seat.
I hope, is everyone okay?
I'm sorry.
Well, I'm a little bit dizzy.
I'm sorry, guys.
I can see in the corner of my eye,
the numbers falling.
Why do I do that?
Why do I purposely do that?
Hopefully, I just hope that the right,
you're having a seizure on me.
Oh, I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I'm sorry. Oh, my head is like, I don't know. I love that thing. I'm really into psychedelics
I've done I've done DMT and you know mushrooms and yeah, I mean, I've done a bunch of psychedelics not, you know
I probably have flashbacks once in a while, but
Wow
Yeah, everyone's synchro pup go. Oh my gosh, that was funny. I'm sorry. I didn't mean to do that
I didn't mean to do that. I forgot to tell
No, thank you clowns, that was fun. I mean, I'm sorry guys. I'm sorry. I didn't I didn't want you to
But
Yeah, I kind of I kind of did like that
Fuck
Yeah, so well, I'm gonna try to come tomorrow. Maybe I'll take the weekend off. Maybe saturday sunday
Take a little breather
Take a little repress, but we do guys we have some
Recalling your lawyer. Oh shit. Well, I did say
You want to have a seizure you could have like just a no in lab
Dr. Rabbit. Hey doctor. Are you not your uncle rabbit? Are you there's a guy named uncle rabbit?
He always always perving out on Benny's I don't know
Can you hit the oh sure of course time everybody on the count of three
What do you want to taste after three one two taste the biscuit?
One taste the biscuit
One more time
three two
Taste the biscuit
There we go. I guess it's a biscuit like a mushroom. That'd be kind of interesting. Oh, what if it's like
You know like
A, D, R, E, N, O, C, H, R, O, M, E, or something like that.
But if it's like really dark and it's like they won't,
that's all they wanted to do is like get all my A, D, R, E,
N, O, C, H, R, O, M, E, like levels high
so they can eat my brain someday.
Wouldn't that be interesting?
I don't think so.
Anyway, how are we doing in chat?
I don't know what we're gonna do.
I think there's one more time
to do an apartment cleanup stream.
My apartment's pretty clean.
I cleaned today, actually.
I did laundry, I kind of mopped up.
I did clean the couch off and stuff.
Why is it a mushroom?
I don't know.
I was actually a little friend.
Sent me that clip. I don't know. I think they like probably just found that clip and it just had a mushroom
Maybe it's maybe it's a mushroom biscuit. I don't know
Show the carpet. Um, I did
Here look, here's my carpet. Hold on. You can see a little bit
I don't know if I don't like camera to go out it might go out because every time I touch it seems to go out
But let me see. I mean, it's not perfect, but it's not bad. I mean
It's a terrible now not terrible
I might can't make curtains a little bit faded but
I am kind of interested in looking at at least the new trip kicks and just to see I'm not going to play the whole thing because I was like yesterday but I want to see what they made me into and not not the Jerry Springer one but there's a new I don't like the Jerry Springer guy one I mean you know it's fine with the I don't know where is it I think that there's was the newest one see
It says oh me versus a scrapper army episode and it's a beta versus psyche and then okay
The other one's a Jerry Springer one. Okay. Well, let's just have a quick look. I just want to see like basically the
Basically, oh, I want to see the sorry. I want to see the
My AI in it because I love AI, you know, let's see have a look
Especially let's have a look at it. No, that's not it. Okay, share the screen
Let's have a little look see
They're having a live about me. I'm getting stuff sent to my house.
People looking for scrap metal and stuff, right?
I'm just here to cut a promo, you know?
I feel, Kate, I feel like we're going to war.
The scrapper army is gonna descend onto the fucking Psyche's house once again.
It could be tomorrow, it could be next week.
He'll never know.
But guess what, Psyche?
Those scrapers are coming for you and I hope you get the metal.
I got no medal. I'm sorry. Yeah, psyche. Well, I don't know that he's tweaking out
But the him and beta stuff I think is really getting to him my thing is I've witnessed
multiple
Attempts of him trying to work it out and just talk one-on-one with beta and it's like someone always
intervening
someone
I want him to fight back and I feel like he doesn't get that chance and it's always a dog pile on him
Um, Aldo, will you stay up here or come back up?
If Sike happens to come up at me, let them in if you need to intervene.
Because Bita needs that support because she's too nice.
Sorry, Bita, you're too nice.
We're just done with the drama. Well, you're in the middle of it now.
Because you come in and say, oh, you're too nice, you old friend.
I'm so sick of people saying that. You're obviously not my friend.
You focus on you. I never did anything wrong to you. I never did. What did I do wrong to you?
For you to like, just like, go against me like that.
It's like every day. You know how much I woke up this morning?
People banging on my door. This guy and his granddaughter looking for scrapbook.
But then it happened again. Then it happened again. Then it happened again.
They have that guy on the show. It's a patriotic stuff. I apologize if I would react to it. I'm sorry
if I get in the mood, but it's like
You know my feelings are hurt too and everyone's acting like I'm just this hurtful mean person and I'm not it's like I get pushed into a corner and
I get upset. I
Think it's I think it's getting to him. I almost feel bad. I
My thing is I've witnessed multiple attempts of him trying to work it out and just talk one-on-one with beta
And it's like someone always intervenes
someone and
I'm like, why does it have to be like that?
And always to her benefit it's always someone coming to her
her defense and I kind of
Sort of feel bad a little bit for him because
Yes
His mic is always so quiet and everyone screams over him. It's annoying. Yeah, or like
He said he got kicked off Sam Man's panel like
So that I just feel bad on like a I wish I could um
I want to I want to like take over and scream for him and like fight for it because like I just like oh my god
But this has been going they feel it like this every week. I know it's just I don't feel bad like that beat us
But I like I just want him to have a fighting
And so I just sit there like oh no get louder get assertive
I want him to fight back, and I feel like he doesn't get that chance because it's always a dog pile on your sauce
Not that I take either side. I just want to see him
Him like be able to stand on his own and
battle beta one-on-one
then
It seems like she always has some army behind her and it's
Psyche is literally the male version of Beacon Patriot.
Yeah, it's a lot.
It's a lot of fucking bullshit, Eldo.
I just saw somebody sent me like a screenshot.
Fucking, that's the shit that I got to deal with.
I give like people chances and I got to deal with that.
You know?
Are you serious, Barry?
You're my fucking mod and you're like looking
to fucking give all my information to people.
And then you're telling me you're the person.
W.
um somebody else is like oh my god like betah look look at berry berries like
saying all this fucking shit about you and like egging on freaking like shannon
some lady named shannon up there like always like talking ranting just talking nonsense and
i'm like okay i don't even really like acknowledge you lady i don't know why you think you know so
much about me she's like oh my god betah has like all these videos nude and hunk like money i'm like
mean do you realize psych has no content unless we are the content you know that right i
well i can't believe you did an unbanned like that honestly jeez what happened i can't believe
you did an unbanned there were so many there was like three salmons i didn't even know which one
But you know who wasn't on there?
Psyche. Psyche wasn't on there at all.
He wasn't banned.
I honestly think he is unless somebody wants to admit to it truthfully and prove it to me.
I think he is Psyche HIV and that one did get banned and that's when he was typing under and maybe he didn't realize it.
Well, he's claiming Eldo. He's saying that's Eldo's alt. He was like, Eldo, that's Eldo. Eldo is saying this and that.
Eldo is just saying, Vita, like, why are you banning people and protecting Psyche when he allows people like Vita's uncle as, you know, alt names?
I think it's him.
To words like protecting him. You know, I'll be like, okay fine. I'm gonna delete that. That's a disgusting name
But then he has like people called beat his uncle rolling around in this working chat and he doesn't even give a shit
Do I a nurse all that? Well, I'm telling you I think that
Hw1 is him. I truly do especially after yesterday when he said that he is blocked and after he jumped down like
within less than 30 seconds, he typed something with his name.
You're saying?
I don't believe that because I don't think he would use an alt like that to discuss his own name.
He's very careful.
Oh my God.
We're going to have a discussion, okay?
Christine, you're an idiot.
at this point I would not put anything past him and there is Katie me that's
not real yeah I just found them right now got it yes thank you but he does use
alts
Yeah
He's used all it's but I mean, I don't know if he's gonna go as far as you know
You think like what better way what better way back stage people once I can listen like it's capable of anything
He's capable if he's capable of doing that to his arm
Saying he was asleep when I happen to him then he's capable of making that all
Okay, and that's not me. Okay. I didn't create all he mad because I said leave that all in the chat
It's no it's not wrong with that. Oh, you know, that's the only thing I said, but me being that all no
That's not me. It's too dumb for your site then leave
It's not that hard leave
It's okay site because remember people's names are in there people's dogs animals are there
Be careful
I saw it in Kim K's chat somebody sent me a screenshot where Barry's like Vita bitch
I could have offered I could have paid got paid for a hundred
It's like why would you even say that like if you want to go ahead and get the money?
Why you know, why are you saying that like I thought you were like cool with me Barry?
I don't get that shit at all. This nigga Barry was blazing saying and talking about cook VB cook VB
I need you to come up here to cook VB
I mean, no disrespect to Shannon, but then she couldn't even hear her.
She lost her voice.
Like, you know what I'm saying?
What the fuck?
Come on, man.
Shannon said she was going to retire.
Shannon, stick to being retired, you know, stay off the internet, Shannon.
Yeah, I'm saying no disrespect man or disrespectfully. I don't really care, but you know, I'm saying like yes
Yeah, I mean like that's it was this wack
She said I apologize to her what the fuck did I apologize to her for I've never had to apologize to her
I've never done shit to her
The only thing I ever said is like I don't really like fuck with her because I know she's going through her medical stuff and all that stuff
But I don't really want to shun it
I was like, I don't you know, I wish her that like she has a good recovery and all that stuff
But what the fuck do I need to apologize to her for she made up a bunch of stories about me because she thinks like raging
Demon is some great white and night like, you know, I don't know if somebody with credibility and so honest
And she was like saying that he said like pictures of me like videos on me fool-naked
I don't have that like are you kidding me from raging demon?
She's like well, I won't show like that like I don't I have it with you first of all
You're saying you have videos of me in your phone
Which do not exist and second of all you
Because you're not like that, but you're gonna bring it up like in life. She lies a lot
She she lies a lot that woman Shannon lies a lot. Yes, I have to step down
I have to handle a few things but
although
Will you stay up here or come back up if Sike happens to come up at me, let them and then if
you need to intervene because Bita needs that support because she's too nice. Sorry, Bita,
you're too nice. I love you, Christine. You're so sweet. Yeah, I tried. I did try. Time said she
could go one-on-one. I don't know, maybe Ms. Nurse said, but no, she wasn't planning on doing that.
She was going to have about five people up there.
Sam and Eldo, I mean, what's the fuck? Isn't she ridiculous? Oh, no conditions
All I said is that can we go one-on-one and then not since someone you know
Someone sends money to clap me in the middle of my sentence not to clap me which happened on salmon the last three times
What happened on summer's channel so and then she is clapping she clapped my friend for five dollars, right?
Talk about you know. Oh my god. I'm my desperation. There's one person defending me one time. She kicks him off
for five dollars, right? I never slapped anyone for five dollars, except it was like, you know,
five dollars a minute or five dollars for five minutes or something like that.
Yeah, it's ridiculous. It's ridiculous. It's stupid. It's like, I tried. Guys, I tried. I did try.
I thought I was live. I was live. And then I ended because I thought she was gonna
do a one-on-one with me. You know, like a lot of people in chat would like to see that.
I just don't understand why she can't talk to me without other people there like she needs like the support like she like
And also she used to put conditions on me all the time. Oh my gosh, you know, I'm I'm gonna
I'm never coming back here again unless you do this unless you do this. That's what she'd always say, right?
She told me to kick people up I know she you know
she's a she's a coward just coward yeah go ahead and talk about KK salmon like
that's so interesting KK is a nice person salmon's a nice person
whatever it's not that interesting to me i don't understand the whole KK
salmon stuff who really i mean go talk about that just stop using me for content though
because when i went over there you're all talking about me you name the stream referencing me
I'm doing I thought it was worth maybe say salvaging a relationship, but it's not there. Come on very calm
Watch back watch back yesterday saying watch the trip pick things. You can just see I just get bulldozed
It's not fair
So if I set a condition for like 10 minutes, what is it? She's on for like 12 hours at a time
What's 10 minutes to like not have a bunch of like, you know
People like echoing in the background. I don't know I guess it's not worth it. I'm not worth it to her
She's not worth it to me. You're right charisma. I give up. I just give up on that. That is just one
That is just one rabbit hole. You don't want to go down
It's just fucking ridiculous
We got Dan Diculus
Right
Emma and Clumsy. Oh, cry me a river!
Good!
What's so cute inside? What are you going to come here and yell at me?
After a year, it's pretty sad that you run to Bita.
You run to Bita to tell.
Oh, Bita! He's as good as he's sulking about. He's going to show.
Like, what the fuck? I know that was you.
Wait, is it reasonable to ask for a one-on-one?
I don't know.
No, run to Bita. Run to Bita.
Go to beat us. She'll give you a platform. Oh, I introduced you. That's what's annoying.
You bring up Emma and clumsy. How about like, those are my relationships to worry about.
How about you stay out of what that, right? You don't know what happened in those relationships.
I had you fucking promote it on my new website.
You're just done with the drama. Well, you're in the middle of it now because you come in and say, oh, you're doing this to your old friends
I'm so sick of people saying that. They're obviously not my friends
You focus on you and I never did anything wrong to you. I never did. What did I do wrong to you?
For you to like just like go against me like that
Thought we were friends
Right well, it was a surprise the website's not up yet. I was gonna like show you but yeah, I'm yeah
I'm kidding you. Well, I'll be sure to take you off. All it was to do is promote you. All it was to do is try to help. I
Didn't try to help you. I didn't introduce you guys
Plus I don't forget what you did, but you got you tried to get me clipped. I'm thinking that
What are you talking about you nut?
Here's nuts. I'm about to block you in the chat. What the fuck?
So silly and I remember when when the whole clumsy thing happened. Well, I was blocked immediately in your chat
You left my discord right over the clumsy. I mean what without about yeah, I don't know. What did I do?
I still don't know I still don't know and I didn't try to get you clipped on anything
You were on her damn show and trip kick click you do you think I I controlled trip kick?
No
You think
See these are called turncoats and then I say oh gypsy was such a good friend to you. Oh, yeah
Does she look does you hear me after she say hey, what's going on? No, she always just runs to beat
Oh, you know, it's like girls club. It's gonna be girls club. I'm wrong cuz I'm a male, right? I
Got your name wrong. Well, I'm sorry. So you have gypsy tarot
Your name is not able to be tagged because you have some kind of setting on what the fuck
No time if she doesn't she doesn't time she doesn't you see what yeah, you see look these are these are my friends
These are my friends. Oh, you're giving up all your old friends. Oh
There are people that betrayed me
betrayers
No, she's too cowardly trust me. She's too cowardly
I'll get up at the link down if some if she comes up. I'll do one-on-one. I will but she's not going to whatever what did I do?
Gypsy what did I do what personal stuff what personal stuff crush you? I don't know I don't know
I don't know, I don't know what you're talking about.
I have no idea.
You're just, you drank the Kool-Aid.
It's okay, it's okay.
Everyone does, everyone, like a lot of people do.
I'm not really surprised.
Well, if it's not about Emory Clemsey,
why'd you bring that up first?
You said Emory Clemsey.
People are just hurt.
You don't think they'll betray me on purpose?
What?
It's like, look at all the people that are over there.
It's her mods, that used to be my mods.
There is butt hurt that I unmodded them
or did something, right?
There's no you don't come at me kindly you come at me yelling at me, okay?
I'm self-deflecting what what do you want me to say Teresa?
What do you want me to say? I was with you from the beginning. I was with you from the beginning
Okay, before any of this I brought you into the world, okay?
Yeah, I don't take any credit for it. You say go you but it's fine
Wow
Yeah, I asked you to go to that chat. Did you defend me? No. Did you say one word in defense of me? No, not one word
It's fine. It's fine. I just know what to expect now. Yeah, there is what I mean
That's the biggest thing I did. Oh, I tagged the wrong person. It's called an accident
I mean, it's I don't know. It's getting too dumb for me. It doesn't get too stupid, but let's see the receipts
You're protecting your heart from me. Oh, what did I do to you? You said it was about Emma
You said it was about Emma's discord, right? What did I do to you? Why is it about Emma and what it was?
I mean, it's like Emma and clumsy. You didn't even like those people. I mean, geez maybe you like clumsy, but he certainly didn't like Emma
Anyway, no, but you had enough time to talk to beta about it and say beta
He's asking me to go defend him or something like that because she's like three or four
This is how psyche treats all those friends.
Yeah, like, well, you're not my friend, BG,
so why don't you stay the fuck out of it?
Okay, okay, but did you see what was going on?
Cause the whole thing was about me.
It says, psychy asleep tarot.
It's okay, I know you're already Ricky Klaus.
You're gonna check it out later, you get the replay.
The thing was, that was all slander.
You should see what they talk about me, you know?
Are you my friend, BG?
No.
Yeah, go pick up go pick up Q who maces homeless people. That's fine, right? You can
I'm gonna be on defensive especially
You were just over there and beaters, you know, you don't don't join my panel anymore. You just joined hers
Talk to her. Oh
Sweetheart, you know, it's like I
Am attacked
All I wanted to get all I wanted to do is have 10 minutes with Bita to talk to her if she wanted to
Just try to salvage the friendship because the last three times I've been on
She has been
Attacking me and I mean have you has has to have four or five people on yelling at me
And then the last time they said okay
Well, everyone will mute and nobody muted and people were talking over me and so I left and then they're like well
You ran I didn't run. It's not a fair fight and I don't want to fight. I was trying to have a conversation
She still won't have the conversation and it's like and I asked for that condition
I mean she used to tell me kick this person out of here
Talk about you and me that's what see that's exactly how it should be it's like every day
You know how much I woke up this morning
People banging on my door this guy and his granddaughter looking for scrap metal
If that happens again, then it happens again, then it happens again
They have that guy on the show. It's okay Teresa, and I apologize if I overreacted and sorry
Maybe I misunderstood but it's like
You know my feelings are hurt too and everyone's acting like I'm just this hurtful mean person and I'm not it's like I get pushed into a corner and
I
Get upset and it's like and I'm sorry if I wasn't there for you when you needed me, but I'm here
I mean, it's like I always try to take your calls or call you back or right back. I always will have you on panel
I know and well, actually, they're not they're not bad people. They're nice people some of the people I talked to are really nice
I'm sorry overreacted. I'm just in bad mood about like, you know, Bita won't talk to me for five minutes
Even a minute
YouTube world's not for you, but we're you're in it Teresa, and I'm sorry if I brought you too far into this
Can the drama community by introducing you to her?
I mean, it's like, you know, she's talking about Chona. She's like, oh your Chona just bought you all your subscriptions or whatever
Understand with Chona, right? She doesn't understand. You know, you know how wonderful Chona is?
She's she's like now. She's bad-mouthing Chona, right?
The sweetest like the sweetest lady
I said, Chona, help me get my channel started, not you, Vita.
I had over a thousand people in my chat.
And she's like, oh, you just, she bought all the people.
No, no, no, no, no, no.
Teresa, you were there.
You were in my early lives, right?
There were lots of people on them.
I had at least like 10 people in my very early lives.
When you do like live streams, people can come in and stuff.
And they don't pay for the pizza though.
And so it's not pizza, it's just an unpaid pizza
that I'm expected to pay for.
And so I have to send the disappointed Mexican pizza lady
away and stuff.
Okay, I'm sorry.
Okay, that's like it hurts.
People I love turn on me for her again and again and again.
They got HK Memphis Shea, they got Sweet Pea,
all these people, they're constantly harassing
with the biscuit song.
Look at her thing.
Oh, biscuit queen.
What is it?
Is it about something other than trying to fuck with me?
I don't think so, because that's a 14 year old meme
that she begged me to play on my show.
And I was like, no.
Then I write a biscuit song called Bita's Biscuits.
And it's like, oh, that's harassing.
It was a good nature thing.
I love you, Gaudi.
Oh, Gaudi, I love you, too, on the thing.
I think you're a good person.
I think that it's like, Bita's turned you against me.
I work it out with anybody I think that was another I want to think
I never saw any of that.
I mean, it's, except, you know,
I never saw Kate like defending me like that.
I did see her like one time, like talking about
that kind of the same like similar thing
where she was like, wow, she actually was watching
the Sandman, let me see, hold on, she was watching.
Bita the beta clip and everything with the with the bronze bird and like her yelling at ever me and Kate was like
Oh my god, if I was a
Psyche I would be like annoyed, too, and I'd be like
Now I was like and Kate didn't I didn't even think like you know, I thought pretty much hated me
But that was a really touching actually like
That she stood up for me a little bit like we're like wanting me to stand up for myself. And I should I was you know
I'm gonna try to make my mic louder and
And now I know what to expect
With the you know
Sorry
I love Tracy too. Oh, no Tracy. Oh, yeah, Tracy X the other Tracy
Not so much
That that was one of the people I like asked I said hey, I'm being like criminally harassed
This is like the Tracy with you know, the Michael Tracy. I was like, I'm being criminally harassed and I'm gonna show
She goes she was on this show like in the chat, but so fucking shit. So or like, you know at least in the chat
I don't know and I'm kind of I don't want to like emotional
Where who's got a KKK dog, I don't know they had those
The ghost dog
Okay
Thank you, thank you trip kick that was a good video
But not like I'm not really it's like I don't I don't want to be mad anybody
I always feel bad afterward.
One time, Jamie Rose, I called Jamie Rose a bitch,
one time on my show, and I felt so bad the next day.
And I was like, oh my God, and I apologized,
and I apologized to her, and she didn't even care.
I mean, she didn't even care that I called her that.
You know, it's kind of funny, like, you know.
So some people, I hope Jamie Rose comes back again soon too.
I don't know.
Oh, no, I love you, Trace.
Oh, you're my home girl.
Oh, Joe and Joe, let me see what's Joe saying.
It's a great Thursday.
Today's Wednesday, isn't it?
Is it Thursday?
Oh, it's Wednesday, Joe.
Come on.
Well, you know, I do feel like I have like a protector and it's like my inner self and it's like and she's like
you know, she's a Scorpio, you know, because I
Know Nick said it was not his favorite song, but I do feel like I
Am protected spiritually
So maybe I'll just wrap up
But I love you guys. Maybe I'll come back. It's 10 o'clock
May it might come back
What's in the future where in the future Oh, it's a one o'clock in the morning on the East Coast your Scorpio Shan well
Because it's like I you know
Isn't it funny like to like my protectors I consider my protector and it's not funny is ever
You know
My
Spirit is like kind of my protector and I feel like the feminine spirit, but
Scorpio got to watch out that the stinger can come out get too close sometimes
Love you guys
Thank you for being here. I'll see you soon